Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 17: Photographs, 1845-circa 2010; 58 Cubic Feet
  - Sub-series 17.6: Color slides, 1950-circa 2010; 6.5 Cubic Feet in nine boxes; in seven boxes and two folders
    - Middle School Camping Trip, Frost Valley, Fall, 1980 (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - Lower School Sailing, April 18, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - Middle School Intensive Term, Catskills, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 12)
    - Awards Chapel, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 13)
    - Clearwater Weekend, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 14)
    - Middle School Moving Up Day, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 15)
    - Shore Ecology, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 16)
    - Princeton Environmental Center, November, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 17)
    - Frost Valley, December, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 18)
    - Field Trip, June, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 19)
    - Field Trip, October, 1982 (Box 239, Folder 20)
    - Outdoor Activities, October, 1982 (Box 239, Folder 21)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Crossing, April, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 22)
    - Field Trip, May, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 23)
    - Outdoor Activities On Brooklyn Bridge, May, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 24)
    - 9th Grade Camping Trip, Class of 1987, Sept, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 25)
    - Maypole, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 26)
    - 9th Grade Camping Trip, Class of 1988, Sept, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 27)
    - Field Trip, October, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 28)
    - Lower School Dancing, Spring, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 29)
    - Lower School Sings, 1986 (Box 239, Folder 30)
    - Dress/Performance "Boys from Syracuse" Act 1, April, 1986 (Box 239, Folder 31)
    - Packer Performance "Boys from Syracuse," April, 1986 (Box 239, Folder 32)
    - Packer Garden Kids' Sculpture, Joralmon Street, May, 1986 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Spring in the Garden, Flowers in Bloom, Joralemon Flags and Flowers, May, 1986 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Bear Mountain, 1987 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Graduation 1987, Slides, Contacts and Prints, Commencement Speaker Mayor Koch (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Mets, June/Pan Am Building, December, 1987 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1988, 6th Graders Frost Valley, 1980s (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Service 1988 Social Action / Brooklyn and Big Apple Circus, 1980s (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Events, circa 1980 (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - 8th Grade Camping Trip, October, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Summer Camp, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - Summer Camp Slide Show, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - Summer Camp Reject Slides, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - 8th Grade Trip, 1994 (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Halloween?, 1995 (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - May Day, 1996 (Box 240, Folder 15)
    - Boys Soccer, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - Girls Soccer, 1980s-1990s (Box 240, Folder 17)
    - Student Performance, 1980s-1990s (Box 240, Folder 18)
    - May Day, 1990s (Box 240, Folder 19)
    - Music Events, 1990s (Box 240, Folder 20)
    - October Field Trip, 1990s (Box 240, Folder 21)
    - Recital, 1994 (Box 240, Folder 22)
    - Recitals, 1990s (Box 240, Folder 23)
    - Yellow Brick Road, 1990s (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Events, 1990s (Box 241, Folder 2)
      includes images dating back to early 1950s
  - Sub-series 17.7: Postcards, circa 1890s-1995; 0.1 Cubic Feet in twelve folders
    The sub-series contains postcards, dating from circa 1890s to 1995. The postcards primarily feature Packer buildings (interiors and exteriors).
    - Building exterior and chapel interior postcards, circa 1890s-1940 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - "Joralemon Street Front Gate with Proposed New Building" postcard, 1900s (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Garden postcard, 1900s (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Principal and the Library postcard, circa 1900s (Box 304, Folder 27)
    - Packer postcards, circa 1900s (Box 104, Folder 9)
      Appear to be early representations of Packer, created by National Art Views Co. N.Y., N.Y.
    - Building postcards, 1907 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Garden sun dial postcard, 1907 (Box 522, Folder 7)
      Donated in memory of Martha Atwater in 2013
    - Postcards, 1900s-1910s (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Postcards, 1900s-1930s (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - Building postcards, 1900s-1960s (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence of Miss Hart, postcard, 1913 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Cape Cod, Coast Guard Station postcard – Addressed to Becky Aldag from Mr. Jensen - Oversize, 1995 (Box 322, Folder 20)
- Series 18: Audio, film, and video recordings, 1931-2013; 14.5 Cubic Feet
  The series contains audiovisual recordings in a variety of formats, including VHS cassettes, Betamax cassettes, Hi-8 cassettes, 8 mm cassettes, 3/4 inch tapes, 16 mm film reels, Mini DVs, DVDs, and audio cassettes. Subjects vary, and include events (especially graduation ceremonies), student theatrical performances, interviews with students and alumni, educational films, teacher seminars, and promotional videos. The tapes and reels date from 1933 to 2010.
  The series is organized into five sub-series:
  Sub-series 18.1: Packer Institute Day in the Life Production
  Sub-series 18.2: Film reels
  Sub-series 18.3: Audio recordings
  Sub-series 18.4: Video recordings
  Sub-series 18.5: Theatrical recordings
  - Sub-series 18.1: Packer Institute Day in the Life Production, 1995-1996; 7.5 Cubic Feet in sixteen boxes
    This sub-series consists of Packer Institute's Day in the Life school production materials. Arranged by material type, this sub-series covers a time span of 1995-1996, with a significant portion highlighting 1995. A Day in the Life series highlights interview questions and discussions asked to a select 17 students and staff at Packer Institute to show the impact of Packer on their lives as well as show how they impact life at Packer. Interviewees are asked about academics, extracurricular activities, the building and grounds, interactions with students and faculty, and every day occurrences at Packer.
    The 17 students and faculty interviewed for this production were: Erin Burke, Simone Callendar, Garfield Davidson, Abigail Hooper, Peter Kelly, Vanessa Olivieri, Chartey Quanceo, Susan Roos, Alliyah Rosenthall, Cynthia Rothschild, Ken Rush, Barbara Seadon, Denise Schweid, Ben Shopsin, Sueta Srinivasen, Laura Zinck, and Erland Zygmuntowicz.
    Materials and Condition: Media formats include beta video tapes, Sony digital audio tapes, Hi8 tapes, and 3/4 inch tapes. A majority of the media used for this production was recorded by Winton DuPont Films. There are also film scripts and interview questions which are both on camera and off, and production notes. Film scripts are in good condition and transcribed by Herman S. Jaffe.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Winton DuPont Films Packer, November 10, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Winton DuPont Films Packer, November 10, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Winton DuPont Films Packer, November 10, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Winton DuPont Films Packer, November 11, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Winton DuPont Films Packer, November 11, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Barbara Seadon Interview, November 11, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Susan Roos / Aliyah Rosenthal Interviews, November 11, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 7)
      Conditions Governing Access
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0002) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Aliyah Rosenthal / Erin Burke, November 11, 1995 (Box 324, Folder 8)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0003) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Erin Burke / Sueta Srinivasen, November 11, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 1)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0004) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Sueta Srinivasen / Garfield Davidson, November 11, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 2)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0005) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Packer, November 11, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Peter Kelly, November 12, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0006) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Peter Kelly / Ken Rush, November 12, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 5)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0011) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Ken Rush, November 12, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0012) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Ken Rush, November 12, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0013) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Betacam Video Cassettes: Abigail Hooper, November 12, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 8)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0014) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Abigail Hooper / Lila Hooper, November 12, 1995 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0007) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Packer, January 25, 1996 (Box 326, Folder 2 – 5)
    - Packer, January 25, 1996 (Box 326, Folder 6 – 7)
    - "Packer" CR 204 (Color) March 26, 1996 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - "Packer" CR 204 (B & W) March 26, 1996 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - "Packer" March 7, 1996 (Box 327, Folder 3 – 7)
    - Packer, March 8, 1996 (Box 328, Folder 1 – 3)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer 1-5"– 3.5" diskette - MSN/MAE, 1990s (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer"– Large Format 3/4" – November 14, 1995 (Box 328, Folder 5 – 7)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer"– Large Format 3/4" – November 14, 1995 (Box 329, Folder 1 – 6)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer"– Large Format 3/4" – November 14, 1995 (Box 330, Folder 1 – 6)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer"– Large Format 3/4" – November 14, 1995 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Winton DuPont Films – "Packer" January 29, 1996 (Box 331, Folder 2 – 6)
    - Winton DuPont Films, 1996 January 29 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Packer "Color Dailies", 1996 January 29 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Packer "B&W Dailies" 1996 January 29 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Packer, 1996 Feburary 15 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Packer, 1996 March 11 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Packer, 1996 March 11 (Box 333, Folder 1 – 6)
    - Packer, 1996 March 11 (Box 334, Folder 1 – 3)
    - Winton DuPont Films – Packer Girls Varsity Soccer Hi-8 Master, 1995 October 23 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Packer, 1996 April 4 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Packer, 1996 April 4 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Abigail Hooper / Maria Yatrakis, 1995 September 22 (Box 336, Folder 1)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0015) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Ben Shopshin / Laura Zinck 1995 September 22 (Box 336, Folder 2)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0016) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Denise Schweid, Cynthia Rothchild, Erin Burke, Undated (Box 336, Folder 3)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0017) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Erland Zygmuntowicz, Susan Roos, Denise Schweid, Undated (Box 336, Folder 4)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0018) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Erin Burke, Vanessa Olivier, Undated (Box 336, Folder 5)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0019) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Interviews with Chartey Quanceo, Garfield Davidson, Sueta Srinivasen, Simone Callendar, Peter Kelly, 1995 October 20 (Box 336, Folder 6)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0020) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Abigail Hooper, Maria Yatrakis 10/95, 1995 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Ben Shopsin, Laura Zinck 9/22/95, 1995 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Chartey Quanceo, Garfield Davidson, Sueta Srinivasen, 1990s (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Erland Zygmuntowicz, Susan Roos, Denise Schweid, 1990s (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Nick Grossman, Meredith Moore, Aliyah Rosenthal, 1990s (Box 336, Folder 11)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0021) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Packer – Upper Class Chorus – Gabe Paquette, 1995 June 6 (Box 336, Folder 12)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0022) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Packer – Award Ceremony, 1995 June (Box 336, Folder 13)
      Recording could not be digitized due to condition of original.
    - Packer – Andy Interview, 6th grade Chorus, Genie Interview/The Prism, 1995 June 6 (Box 336, Folder 14)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0024) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - Packer, 1995, June 15 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - Packer Girls Varsity Soccer, 1995 October 23 (Box 336, Folder 16)
      This recording (bhs_2014.019_0025) is available onsite at the Brooklyn Historical Society. Please contact library@brooklynhistory.org to make an appointment in advance of your visit.
    - 38 Packer, 1996 April 5 (Box 336, Folder 17)
    - Transcripts, October 20 1995 (Box 336, Folder 18, Disk digital files)
      Donated on one 3 1/2 inch floppy disk containing four digital files. Digital ID 2014_019_media_020.
    - Schedules, Lists, Correspondence, Undated (Box 336, Folder 19)
    - Preliminary Background on Subjects, Undated (Box 336, Folder 20)
    - Question List for Interviews, Undated (Box 336, Folder 21)
    - Video Log Sheet, Undated (Box 336, Folder 22)
    - "Packer" Tape 1 Transcript – Interview with Abigail Hooper (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Interview Transcript Ben Shopsin and Laura Zinck, 1995, October 11 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Interview Transcript with Denise Schweid, Cynthia Rothschild and Erin Burke, 1995 October 11 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Interview Transcript with Erland Zygmuntowicz, Susan Ross and Denise Schweid, 1995 October 13 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Interview Transcript with Erland Zygmuntowicz, Susan Ross and Denise Schweid, 1995 October 13 (Box 527, Folder 25)
    - Interview Transcript with Erin Burke, Susan Ross, Barbara Seadon, Undated (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Transcript - Erin Burke, Vanessa Olivieri, and Barbara Seadon, 1995 October 13 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Transcript w/Chartey Quanceo, Garfield Davidson, Sueta Srinivasen, Simone Callendar, Peter Kelly, 1995 October 20 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Various Interview Transcripts, 1995 October 20 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Interview Transcripts, Erin Burke, Abigail Hooper, Peter Kelley, Susan Ross, Allyah Rosenthal, Undated (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Interview Transcript – Garfield Davidson and Barbara Seadon, Undated (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Interview Transcript – Garfield Davidson, Sueta Srinivasen and Peter Kelly, Undated. (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Varied Interviews – Packer High School, Undated. (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - "Packer School" 204 – Interview Transcripts with tape time notation – Susan Roos, Allyah Rosenthal, Garfield Davidson, Undated (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Interviews w/Peter Kelly, Garfield Davidson, Ken Rush and Abigail Hooper, Undated. (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Sub-series 18.2: Film reels, 1931-1972; 1.1 Cubic Feet in three boxes
    This sub-series contains 16mm and Super 8 films, dating from 1931 to 1972. They include footage of Packer events, educational films, and one student film ("Exitus").
    - "Packer Collegiate Institute Class Day 1931." (Box 339, Folder 1)
      Film stock on metal reel with original cardboard container. Written in blue ink on container front. "Packer \ Class Day \ 1931." Written on container bottom. "DENTON." Written in pencil in upper-right corner of container back. "6044-1 \ Dupe-102." Written in pencil in upper left corner of container back. "K." Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 50' in length, B&W, silent. Very poor condition. Film curls and twists when unwound. Leader is dry and brittle. Original container in poor condition. Film stock is dented.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 2)
      Film stock on a metal reel. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 50' in length, B&W, silent, edge code. Poor condition. Stock has an odor, twists and curls when it is unwound. Dry, brittle leader.
    - Dance, spring, 1958 (Box 339, Folder 3)
      Film stock in a metal reel with original cardboard Kodak container. Written in blue ink on front of container. "DANCE \ PACKER. SPRING, 1958." Large Roman numeral II scribbled onto front in blue/green crayon and crossed out with blue ink. Processing label from "Borough Hall Camera Shop" adhered to bottom of container. Reel flanges are tight/bent and prevent stock from easily unwinding. Imprinted into stock along edge. "PROCESSED BY KODAK MAY 58". "PROCESSED BY KODAK" printed on leader. Emulsion maintained bright, vivid colors. Kodak Safety film, 16 mm, color, 50' in length. Good condition. Dry and brittle leader. No scent to film.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 4)
      Film stock in metal reel. Safety film, color, 50' in length, silent. Edge code. Poor condition.Very loose on reel. Vinegar scent.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 5)
      Film stock on a metal reel. Stock features color footage of an outdoor school event. Kodachrome film, 16mm, 50' in length, color. Edge code.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 6)
      Film stock on a metal AFGA reel. Reel not unwound due to flaking emulsion. This is the only AFGA reel in the collection. 16mm, 50' in length.Very, very poor condition. Flaking emulsion. Dry, brittle leader.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 7)
      Film stock in metal reel. Kodak Safety film, 16 mm, 50' in length, B&W, silent. Edge code. Poor condition. Uneven wind. Bent stock at head. Torn sprocket holes at head. Film coils tightly when unwound.
    - "Dancing in the Garden.", 1945 (Box 339, Folder 8)
      Film stock on a metal reel. Written in cursive on leader in ink. "Dancing in the garden –Centennial Year, 1945 May 9." Kodak Kodachrome, 16mm, 50' in length, color, silent. Edge code. Good condition.
    - Untitled ["Miss Hickock, Packer Institute"], 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 9)
      Film stock in metal reel with original cardboard container. Written in ink on back of container. "Miss Hickock, Packer Institute." Kodak Kodachrome, 16mm, 50' in length, Color, silent. Edge code. Good condition.
    - Untitled, 1930s-1950s (Box 339, Folder 10)
      Film stock in plastic reel, with original cardboard container. Stock contains vivid color footage of an outdoor event. First eight frames perforated with a numeric code. "26372505." Fair condition. Film has an odor. Needs a new leader.
    - Mailing Containers, 1941-1953 (Box 339, Folder 11)
      Four Kodak post-processing mailing containers (2 are Kodachrome): May 21, 1953; Undated; Kodachrome, Undated - "Develop Before" 1944 January; Kodachrome, Undated - "Develop Before" 1941 January
    - Untitled., 1930s-1950s (Box 340, Folder 1)
      Film stock on a metal reel. Stock not unwound due to condition. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 200', B&W, silent. Edge code. + Poor condition. Bent, dented, torn film stock. No leader. Torn sprocket holes. Loose wind. Slight vinegar scent.
    - "Colonial Children.", 1930s-1950s (Box 340, Folder 2)
      Film stock on metal reel found inside original metal canister. Yellow and blue label on can lid reads. "COLONIAL CHILDREN \ An Erpi Classroom Film \ ENCYCLOPEDIA BRITANNICA FILMS, INC. \ 1841 Broadway, New York 23, N.Y." Film not unwound due to condition. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 400" in length, B&W, silent. Edge code. Poor condition.Very strong vinegar scent. Leader is brittle and warping. Reel flanges are loose and rusty. Stock is brittle and warped with torn sprocket holes.
    - Untitled., 1930s-1950s (Box 340, Folder 3)
      Film stock on metal reel in original metal canister with desiccated paint on can bottom. Three lines of illegible cursive writing on top can lid. Illegible print handwritten in pencil on reel flange. Stock was slightly unwound to identify film content. detached stock is a length of title frames ("From Osh Kosh to Anywhere") spliced to stock featuring a woman's face, spliced to animates frames. Animation on detached stock matches stock in reel. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 200' in length, B&W, sound, + Poor condition. Tight wind. Broken sprocket holes. Stock is warping and brittle in places.
    - "Puppet Show / 4th Grade Play / 6th Grade Play", 1930s-1950s (Box 340, Folder 4)
      Film stock in metal reel. Partially illegible pencil inscription on reel. Stock not unwound due to condition. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 250' in length, B&W, silent. Edge code. + Poor condition. Stock and emulsion is scratched. Film has a slight odor. Stock is bent with torn sprocket holes. No leader, no can.
    - "Packer Coll. Institute.", 1930s-1950s (Box 340, Folder 5)
      Film stock in metal reel. 3" x ½" rectangular discoloration on reel near flange edge; written on discoloration in pencil. "Packer Coll Inst". First hundred frames of film stock feature students entering and exiting Packer Collegiate's main entrance and students in a swimming pool. Kodak Safety film, 16mm, 400' in length, B&W, silent. Edge. Poor condition. Uneven wind with loose film stock. Stock is torn, bent, warped, and has torn sprocket holes. No can.
    - "Exitus", 1972 (Box 527, Folder 24)
      Super 8 film that includes members of classes 1972-1975. Film was shot in April 1972. It is the mini-term project of a group who took a trip to Israel.
  - Sub-series 18.3: Audio recordings, 1946-1999
    The sub-series contains audio recordings on cassettes and magnetic tapes, dating from 1946 to 1999. They include recordings of Packer events, educational conferences, and interviews with Packer alumni.
    Sub-sub-series 18.3.1: Events and other recordings
    Sub-sub-series 18.3.2: Interviews
    - Sub-sub-series 18.3.1: Events and other recordings, 1946-1999; 2.2 Cubic Feet in seven boxes